{
    "subject": "resource/Peter_Raw",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfDeath",
    "object": "1988-07-14",
    "human_readable": "Peter Raw died on July 14, 1988.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8302656412124634,
            "question": "When did Peter Raw die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8137709498405457,
            "question": "Did Peter Raw live past 1988?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7878738045692444,
            "question": "Was Peter Raw alive in 1989?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7628124356269836,
            "question": "Is July the month of Peter Raw's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7245334386825562,
            "question": "What month did Peter Raw die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6554010510444641,
            "question": "What is the date of Peter Raw's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5854424238204956,
            "question": "What is the day of Peter Raw's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48734232783317566,
            "question": "In what year did Peter Raw pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45561617612838745,
            "question": "How would you express the date of Peter Raw's death in full?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.047901809215545654,
            "question": "Is July a summer month?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Peter Raw died on July 14, 1988.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6854_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you express the date of Peter Raw's death in full?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6854_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Peter Raw pass away?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6854_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the day of Peter Raw's death?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6854_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6854_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6854_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6854_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6854_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6854_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6854_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6854_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6854_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6854_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6854_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided documents, Air Commodore Peter Frank Raw passed away on July 15, 1988, not July 14, 1988."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information states that Peter Raw died on 15 July 1988, not July 14, 1988.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}